A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Dissertations of Students FA1040
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Dissertations of Students
1948-1997
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University.
Rockefeller Institute
FA1040
20.68 Cubic Feet 47 document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 25 years old are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 475-U
Scope and Contents
Consists of doctoral dissertations of students who attended the Rockefeller Institute/Rockefeller University.
Arrangement
As received.
- Rasmussen, Howard - Studies Upon The Isolation And Properties Of Parathroid Hormone B, 1959 (Box 1)
- Cebra, John J. - The Serologic Reactivity Of Polpeptides From Silk Fibroin: Studies On The Combining Sites Of A Protein Antigen, 1960 (Box 1)
- Fulton, Chander Montgomery - The Biology Of A Colonial Hydroid, 1960 (Box 1)
- Goldberg, Irving H. - Enzymatic Sulfurylation Mechanisms, 1960 (Box 1)
- Hopkins, J. W. - Reactions Governing Amino Acid Incorportaion Into The Proteins Of An Isolated Cell Nucleus, 1960 (Box 1)
- Kirsch, Jack Frederick - Amino Acid Incorporation In Vitro By Ribonucleoprotein Particles Detached From Guinea Pig Liver Microsomes, 1961 (Box 2)
- Greene, Lewis Joel - Comparison Of The Protein Contents Of Bovine Granules And Of The Pancreatic Juice, 1962 (Box 2)
- Karlin, Arthur - The Inactivation Of Neurohypophyseal Hormones By The Toad Bladder, 1962 (Box 2)
- Loeb, Tim - An RNA Containing Bacteriophage Specific For The F+ Hfr Mating Types Of Escherichia Coli K-12, 1962 (Box 2)
- Luck, David J. L. - Glycogen Synthesis From Uridine Diphoshate Glucose: The Relation Of The Enzyme To Glycogen Deposits And Membranes In The Liver Cell, 1962 (Box 2)
- Vanable, Joseph William, Jr. - Morphological And Biochemical Studies On The Emergence Of The Granular Glands During Metamorphosis Of Xenopus Laevis, 1962 (Box 3)
- Bloom, Barry Robert - Studies On The Delay - Type Hypersensitivity Including Attempts To Effect Transfer In Guinea Pigs With Subcellular Materials, 1963 (Box 3)
- Davidson, Eric Harris - The Expression Of Differentiated Character In Monolayer Tissue Culture Cells, 1963 (Box 3)
- Gomatos, Peter John - Animal And Plant Viruses With Double-Stranded Ribonucleic Acid, 1963 (Box 3)
- Guidotti, Guido - Studies On Th e Chemistry Of Human Hemoglobin, 1963 (Box 3)
- Hershey, John William Baker - The Chemical Synthesis Of Model Catalysts Related To Enzymes, 1963 (Box 4)
- Reich, Edward - Some Aspects of Nucleic Acid Function Studied with Actinomycin and Mitomycin, 1963 (Box 4)
- Gally, Joseph Anthony - Physiochemical Studies Of The L Polypeptide Chains In Y-Globulins And Bence-Jones Proteins, 1964 (Box 4)
- McEwen, Bruce Sherman - Energy Metabolism In Cell Nuclei, 1964 (Box 4)
- Burgess, Paul R. - A Study Of The Transmission Of Sensory Information In The Cat Spinal Cord, 1965 (Box 4)
- Cellarius, Richard Andrew - A Model For The Chloroplast: A Study Of The Photochemical And Spectral Properties Of Th e Pheophytin A Absorbed To The Surface Of Small Particles, 1965 (Box 5)
- Greene, Lorna - Studies On The Granule-Moving System Of Melanocytes Of Fundulus Heteroclitus, 1965 (Box 5)
- Hille, Merrill Burr - The Application Of A Reporter Group To A-Chymotrypsin, 1965 (Box 5)
- Tomasi, Thomas Bartholomew, Jr. - Studies On The Immunoglobulin A Protein Of Serum And Nonvascular Fluids, 1965 (Box 5)
- Bowers, William E. - A Biochemical Characterization Of Rat Spleen Lysosomes And Lysosomes From Other Lymphoid Tissues, 1966 (Box 5)
- Jamieson, James D. - Intracellular Transport Of Secretory Protein: Role Of The Golgi Complex, 1966 (Box 6)
- Krug, Robert M. - Double-Helical Reovirus RNA As Template For Nucleic Acid And Protein Synthesis, 1966 (Box 6)
- Cerami, Anthony - Biochemical Studies Of The Purine Analogues, 2-Aminopurines and 2,6 Diaminopurine, 1967 (Box 6)
- Engelhardt, Dean Lee - The Translation In Vitro Of Coliphage f2 RNA Containing Amber Suppressible Codons, 1967 (Box 6)
- Tidwell, James Thomas - The Biological Methylation of Histones, 1967 (Box 6)
- Williams, Robley C., Jr. - The Non-covalent Association Of Tyrocidine B, 1967 (Box 7)
- Bennett, Gudrun Staub - The Isolation And Characterization Of Soluble Brain Proteins, 1968 (Box 7)
- Bradbury, Jack W. - Mechanisms Of Target Discrimination By The Echolocating Bat, Vampyrum Spectrum, 1968 (Box 7)
- Brayshaw, David Douglas - On The Off-Shell Solution Of Scattering Equations, 1968 (Box 7)
- Cass, Albert - Water And Ion Permeability Of Thin Lipid Membranes, 1968 (Box 8)
- Compans, Richard W. - The Structure And Replication Of A Parainfluenza Virus, 1968 (Box 8)
- Ehrenreich, Barbara A. - The Intracellular Fate of Pinocytosed Proteins And Peptides, 1968 (Box 8)
- Grundy, Scott M. - Regulation Of Cholesterol Concentrations In Man, 1968 (Box 9)
- Herron, Helen Arnold - The Development Of Photosynthesis In A Greening Mutant Of Chlorella, 1968 (Box 9)
- Hirsch, David I. - The Hydroxamate Reaction Of Aminoacyl -tRNA Synthetases, 1968 (Box 9)
- Hirsch, David I. - The Hydroxamate Reaction Of Aminoacyl -tRNA Synthetases, 1968 (Box 10)
- Holmes, Kathryn V. - Cell Fusion Induced By The Parainfluenza Virus SV5, 1968 (Box 10)
- Kapuler, A. M. "An Analysis Of The Stereochemical Requirements For The Synthesis Of Polynucleotides By DNA Dependent Nucleic Acid Polymerases, 1968 (Box 10)
- Kleinsmith, Lewis, J. - Phosphoproteins Of The Cell Nucleus: Metabolism And Characterization, 1968 (Box 11)
- Murphy, Thomas J. - Correction To The Debye-Huckel Theory, 1968 (Box 11)
- Parr, Earl - Uterine Foreign Bodies: Inflamation And Contraception, 1968 (Box 11)
- Poole, Brian - Studies Of Rat Liver Peroxisomes, 1968 (Box 11)
- Price, Pau l A. - Chemical Studies On Pancreatic Deoxyibonuclease, 1968 (Box 11)
- Rifkin, Daniel B. - Chemical Studies On Mouse Hemogloin, 1968 (Box 11)
- Sturman, Lawrence S. - Host -Dependent Restriction Of The Replication Of A Piconavirus, 1968 (Box 12)
- Williams, Timothy C. - Nocturnal Orientation Techniques Of A Neotropical Bat, 1968 (Box 12)
- Acheson, Nicholas H. - The Structure And Replication Of Semiliki Forest Virus, A Mosquito Borne Animal Virus, 1969 (Box 12)
- Carr, Ronald I. - DNA Antibodies And DNA In Serum, 1969 (Box 12)
- Cheng, Ta -Pei - Radiative Corrections To Low Energy Theorems, 1969 (Box 13)
- Cushman, Samuel W. - Hormonal Effects On The Ultrastructure And Metabolism of Isolated Adipose Cells, 1969 (Box 13)
- Ehrenreich, John H. - The Golgi Complex Of The Hepatocyte: Isolation And Partial Enzmological Characterization, 1969 (Box 13)
- Ensminger, William D. - Viral Inhibition Of Mammalian Cell DNA Synthesis, 1969 (Box 13)
- Ensminger, William D. - Viral Inhibition Of Mammalian Cell DNA Synthesis, 1969 (Box 14)
- Finch, Caleb Ellicott - Cellular Activities During Ageing In Mammals, 1969 (Box 14)
- Fowler, Stanley Dee - Lepolytic Activites Of Rat Liver Lyposomes, 1969 (Box 14)
- Fox, Ronald Forrest - Contributions To The Theory Of Non-Equilibrium Thermodynamics, 1969 (Box 15)
- Grunbaum, Francisco Alberto - Some Problems Connected With The Bollzmann Equation, 1969 (Box 15)
- Hascall, Vincent C., Jr. - Protein polysaccharides From Bovine Nasal Cartilage Interactions With Glycoproteins And The Formation Of Aggragates, 1969 (Box 15)
- Hascall, Vincent C., Jr. - Protein polysaccharides From Bovine Nasal Cartilage Interactions With Glycoproteins And The Formation Of Aggragates, 1969 (Box 16)
- Herron, David Kent - I. Solution Photochemistry Of Camphor, II. Synthesis And Solution Photochemistry of 2, 2-Dimethylcyclobutanone, 1969 (Box 16)
- Hildebrand, John G. - Succinyl Phosphates And The Succinyl Coenzyme A Synthetase Reaction, 1969 (Box 16)
- Kleinberg, Eugene M. - Strong Partition Properties For Infinite Cardinals, 1969 (Box 17)
- Leskes, Andrea - The Localization Of Glucose-6-Phosphatase In Developing Rat Liver: A Histochemical And Biochemical Study, 1969 (Box 17)
- Meins, Frederick, Jr., - Control Of Phenotypic Expression In Tobacco Teratoma Tissues, 1969 (Box 17)
- Millecchia, Lyndell Larsen - Embryogenesis in the Suctorian Tokophrya Infusion: A Light and Electron Microscope Study, 1969 (Box 18)
- Millecchia, Ronald - The Ventral Photoreceptor Cells Of Limulus: An Electrophysiological Study, 1969 (Box 18)
- O'Neil, Patrick Eugene - Asymptotic Enumerations For 0-1 Matrices, 1969 (Box 18)
- Peterson, Barry W. - A Single Unit Analysis Of The Properties And Distribution Of Gravity Responses In, The Vestibular Nuclei Of The Cat, 1969 (Box 18)
- Rifkin, Mary R. - Properties Of Beogenesis Of Mitochondrial Ribosomes From Neurospora Crassa, 1969 (Box 19)
- Robertson, Hugh D. - Structure And Function Of An Intermediate In Phage RNA Replication, 1969 (Box 19)
- Rossomando, Edward F. - Studies On The Structure Of Bacteriophage f1, 1969 (Box 19)
- Sajdera, Stanley, W. - Organization of Proteinpolysacchorides and Collagen in Cartilage Matrix, 1969 (Box 19)
- Snodderly, D. Max Jr. - Processing of Visual Inputs By The Ancient Brain of Limulus, 1969 (Box 19)
- Spencer, Martin E. - Structural Studies on Bovine Plasma Albumin, 1969 (Box 20)
- Ward, David C. - Biochemical Studies on Nucleotide and Polynucleotide Analogs, 1969 (Box 20)
- Schor, Seth Lawrence - Rugular Variations in Chloroplast Functional Activity During the Division Cycle of Chlamydomonas Reinhardi, 1971 (Box 20)
- Fedoroff, Nina V. - Purification and Properties of Bacteriophage f2 Replicase, 1972 (Box 20)
- Gray, Peter - A Mineralocorticoid-Dependent Effects of Prestress on Avoidance Responding in Rats, 1972 (Box 21)
- Nist, Cynthia R. - Studies on Rapidly Labelled RNA from Mitochondrial Polysomes of Neurospora Crassa, 1972 (Box 21)
- Greco, Frank Anthony - The Formation of Channels in Lipid Bilayers by Gonococcal Major Outer Membrane Protein, 1981 (Box 21)
- Baltimore, David - The Diversion of Macromolecular Synthesis in L-Cells Towards Ends Dictated by Memgovirus, 1964 April 15 (Box 21)
- Acheson, Nicholas H. - The Structure and Replication of Semliki Forest Virus A Mosquito?Borne Animal Virus, 1969 April 21 (Box 22)
- Ensminger, William D. - Viral Inhibition of Mammalian Cell DNA Synthesis, 1969 April 11 (Box 22)
- Burlingham, Byron T. - Characteristics of an Endonuclease Associated with Adenovirus Types 2 and 12, 1970 May 15 (Box 22)
- Mosser, Anne G. - Poliovirus Replication: Interaction with Cytoplasmic Membranes and with Compounds which Affect Virus Biosynthesis, 1971 March 15 (Box 23)
- Lazarowitz, Sondra G. - Synthesis and Processing of Influenza Virus-Specific Proteins, 1975 April 11 (Box 23)
- Burger, Harold - The Integration of Adenovirus DNA into the DNA of Productively Infected Human Cells, 1976 March 15 (Box 23)
- Sehgal, Parvinkumar B. - Regulation of Gene Expression in Human Cells: RNA Synthesis and Interferon Production, 1977 February 7 (Box 24)
- Jasny, Barbara R. - The Organization of DNA Replication in Mammalian Cell Lines, 1978 April 1 (Box 24)
- Silver, Samuel M. - The Proteins of Measles Virus and Their Synthesis in Infected Cells, 1978 August 30 (Box 24)
- Wheelock, E. Frederick - Cellular Respose to Multiplication of a Cytocidal Virus, 1961 April 15 (Box 24)
- Wheelock, E. Frederick - Cellular Respose to Multiplication of a Cytocidal Virus, 1961 April 15 (Box 25)
- Bablanian, Rostom H. - Studies on the Mechanism of Entervirus-Induced Cell Damage, 1964 October (Box 25)
- Holmes, Kathryn V. - Cell Fuson Induced by the Parainfluenza Virus SV5, 1968 April 8 (Box 25)
- Balk, Samuel. The Role of Calcium, Serum, Plasma, and Folic Acid in the Control of Proliferation of normal and Rous Sarcoma Virus-Infected Chicken Fibroblasts, 1973 April 1 (Box 25)
- Merz, David Charles - Immunochemical and Biochemical Approaches to Understanding the Biological Roles of Paramyxovirus Envelope Proteins, 1979 April 10 (Box 26)
- Roos, David Siker - Cell Fusion, Lipid Composition, and Tumoringenicity of Cultured Cells, 1984 April 23 (Box 26)
- Sagar, Anurag Daya - Expression of the Human Interferon Genes, 1984 March 30 (Box 26)
- JSM - Notes, Graphs and Correspondence Between Jim and Igor, undated (Box 26)
- Osterhout, Suydam - Studies on the Interaction of Herpes Simplex Virus and Human Amnion Cells in Tissue Culture, 1959 May (Box 27)
- Gomatos, Peter John - Animal and Plant Viruses with Double-Stranded Ribonucleic Acid, 1963 April 15 (Box 27)
- Compans, Richard W - The Structure and Replication of a Parainfluenza Virus, 1968 January 25 (Box 27)
- Rivers, Thomas M., Editor - Viral and Rickettsial Infections of Man, 1948 (Box 27)
- Rivers, Thomas M., Editor - Viral and Rickettsial Infections of Man, Second Edition, 1952 (Box 28)
- Rivers, Thomas M., Editor - Viral and Rickettsial Infections of Man, Third Edition, 1959 (Box 28)
- Dubos, Rene J., Editor - Bacterial and Mycotic Infections of Man, 1948 (Box 29)
- Dubos, Rene J., Editor - Bacterial and Mycotic Infections of Man, Second Edition, 1952 (Box 29)
- Dubos, Rene J., Editor - Bacterial and Mycotic Infections of Man, Third Edition, 1958 (Box 30)
- Bennett, Thomas P. - The Charging and Coding Specificities of Soluble RNA, 1965 March 31 (Box 30)
- Cerami, Anthony - Biochemical Studies of the Purine Analogues, 2-Aminopurine and 2,6 Diaminopurine, 1967 April 1 (Box 30)
- Hirsh, David I. The Hydroxamate Reaction of Aminoacyl-tRNA Synthetases, 1968 March 28 (Box 30)
- Wolfenden - Some Characteristics of the Linkage of Amino Acids to Soluable RNA, 1964 (Box 31)
- Spyrides, George J. - Macromolecular Interactions in Peptide Synthesis in Escherichia Coli, 1963 (Box 31)
- Kapuler, A. M. An Analysis of the Stereochemical Requirements for the Synthesis of Polynucleotides by DNA Dependent Nucleic Acid Polymerases, 1968 April 1 (Box 31)
- Krisko, Istvan. Species Specificity in Peptide Synthesis, 1970 March 30 (Box 31)
- Marshall, G. R. - Studies on Solid-Peptide Synthesis, 1966 March 31 (Box 31)
- Rifkin, Daniel B. - Chemical Studies on Mouse Hemoglobin, 1968 May (Box 32)
- Sauer, Leonard A. - Some Studies on the Crabtree Effect in the Ehrlich-Lettre Ascites Tumor, 1966 April 1 (Box 32)
- Schleich, Thomas W. - Gel Filtration Heterogeneity of Soluble RNA: A Study of the Fractionation Products, 1966 March 15 (Box 32)
- Carr, Ronald I. - DNA Antibodies and DNA in Serum, 1969 April 11 (Box 32)
- Cebra, John J. - The Serologic Reactivity of Polypeptides From Silk Fibroin: Studies on the Combining Sites of a Protein Antigen, 1960 April 15 (Box 32)
- Prystowsky, Michael B. - Inhibition of the Classical Complement Pathway by Synthetic Peptides from the Cv2 Domain of lmmunoglobulin G (Thesis submitted to The City University of New York), 1978 (Box 33)
- Gottlieb, Alice Bendix - Studies of Human in Vitro Cellular Immune Function in Normal and Disease States, 1979 April (Box 33)
- Tomasi,Thomas B. - Studies on the lmmunoglobulin A Proteins of Serum and Nonvasular Fluids, 1965 May (Box 33)
- Hurley, John N. - Lymphoid Cell Lines from Normal and Leukemic Individuals, 1979 April (Box 33)
- Wang, Chang Yi - Structural and Functional Characterization of Surface Antigens on Human B Lymphocytes, 1979 April (Box 34)
- Briles, David E. - Studies on the Inheritance of ldiotypic Markers of Mouse Antibody to Streptococcal Group A Carbohydrate and on Other Genetic Factors Which Influence the Immune Response, 1973 April 23 (Box 34)
- Spencer, E. Martin - Structural Studies on Bovine Plasma Albumin, 1969 May 1 (Box 34)
- Nussenzweig, Michel C. - Surface and Functional Studies of Mouse Dendritic Cells, 1981 March 1 (Box 34)
- Penn, Gerald Melville - The Comparison of ldiotypic Antigens on Multiple Monoclonal Proteins Within the Same Sera (Thesis submitted to The Ohio State University), 1975 (Box 35)
- Tauber, Jurg W. - The Biology of Group A Streptococcus: From HL-A to Complement, 1975 March 15 (Box 35)
- Guidotti, Guido - Studies on the Chemistry of Human Hemoglobin, 1962 May 10 (Box 35)
- Jerry, L. Martin - Genetic Variability of Interchain Disulfide Bridges in Human Immunoglobulin A2, 1971 March 22 (Box 36)
- Vande Stouwe, Robert Allen - Proliferation Versus Cytotoxic T Cell Generation in Autologous Mixed Lymphocyte Culture Reactions (Thesis submitted to Columbia University), 1977 (Box 36)
- Chen, Chang - The Role of Macrophages in the In Vitro Immune Response, 1973 April (Box 36)
- Devoe, Robert Donald - Electrical Responses to Flicker in the Eye of the Wolf Spider. Lycoso Baltimoriana, 1961 April (Box 37)
- Nardin, Elizabeth Higgins - A Study of the Antibody Response Against the Malaria Sporozoite in Immunized and Naturally Infected Hosts Using the Indirect Immunofluorescent Antibody Technique, undated (Box 37)
- Satir, Peter Gerald - The Mechanism of Ciliary Motion: A Correlation of Morphological and Physiological Aspects of Ciliary Beat of the Gill Epithelium of the Freshwater Mussel., 1961 May (Box 37)
- Bennett, Thomas Peter - The Charging and Coding Specificities of S-RNA, 1965 March 31 (Box 38)
- Weiss, Martin M. - Studies on Plasmodia In Vitro, 1982 June (Box 38)
- Wolk, Coleman Peter - Experimental Studies on the Development of a Blue-Green Algae, 1964 April 15 (Box 38)
- Yamin, Michael A. - Axenic Cultivation and Metabolism of Mutualistic Cellulose-Digesting Flagellates of Termites, 1980 March 3 (Box 38)
- Simpson, Larry, Studies on the Kinetoplast of the Hemoflagellates, undated (Box 39)
- Strauss, Phyllis R. - Acriflavin Resistance in the Hemoflagellate, Leishmonia Tarentolae, 1971 April 1 (Box 39)
- Friedman, Milton J. - Malaria and Red Cell Variants: Models of Host-Cell Competence and Resistance to Disease, 1979 April 20 (Box 39)
- Nagin, Richard - Caste Regulation in the Termite, Neotermes Jouteli, 1970 April 22 (Box 40)
- Meshnick, Steven R - An Approach to the Development of New Drugs for African Trvpanosomiasis, 1978 January (Box 40)
- Ehrenreich, John H. - The Golgi Complex of the Hepatocyte: Isolation and Partial Enzymological Characterization, 1969 April 28 (Box 40)
- Acheson, Nicholas H. - The Structure and Replication of Semliki Forest Virus, a Mosquito-Borne Animal Virus, 1969 April 21 (Box 40)
- Fulpius, Bernard W. - The Acetylcholine Receptor: Isolation and Characterization of a Macromolecule From the Eel, Electrophorus Electricus, 1973 April 15 (Box 41)
- Simon, Sandra R. W. - Preparation and Properties of Membrane Fractions From Rhodospirillum Rubrum, 1972 (Box 41)
- Kirsch, Jack Frederick - Amino Acid Incorporation in Vitro by Ribonucleoprotein Particles Detached From Guinea Pig Liver Microsomes, 1961 April 15 (Box 41)
- Carlin, Richard K. - Studies in Biochemistry: I.The Incorporation of Amino Acids Into Troponin, II. Poly(A): (1) Evolution and Function, (2) The Evolution of Viruses, 1978 May (Box 41)
- Young, Donald Adam - Studies on the Functional Location of Microsomal Enzymes, 1961 May (Box 42)
- Aoki, Chiye, The Role of Hormone-Stimulated cAmp Metabolism in Visual Cortical Plasticity, 1985 March (Box 42)
- Silver, Samuel M. - The Proteins of Measles Virus and Their Synthesis in Infected Cells, 1978 August 30 (Box 42)
- Peluso, Richard W. - Paramyxovirus Replication and Effects on Host Cell Protein Synthesis, 1979 April 2 (Box 43)
- Metroka, Craig E. - Temperature Sensitive Mutants of Rous Sarcoma Virus, 1978 June (Box 43)
- Balk, Samuel - The Role of Calcium, Serum, Plasma, and Folic Acid in the Control of Proliferation of Normal and Rous Sarcoma Virus-Infected Chicken Fibroblasts, 1973 February 1 (Box 43)
- Gross, Janet Lynn - The Effect of Avian Retroviruses on Avian Limb Bud Chondrogenesis in Vitro, 1980 (Box 44)
- Merz, David Charles - Immunochemical and Biochemical Approaches to Understanding the Biological Roles of Paramyxovirus Envelope Proteins, 1979 April 10 (Box 44)
- Karess, Roger E. - Structural and Functional Studies of the Transforming Protein of Recovered Avian Sarcoma Viruses, 1980 July 28 (Box 44)
- Fisch, Tobe Michelle - A Study of the Transcriptional Regulation of the Proto-Oncogene C-Fos: Mechanisms of Induction by EGF, TPA, and A23187, 1988 June (Box 45)
- Kole, Lisa Blanche, The Control of Gene Expression During Murine Erythroleukemia Cell Differentiation, 1985 March 1 (Box 45)
- Kessler, Daniel Solomon - Signal Transduction and Transcriptional Regulation in the Response to Type I Interferon, 1990 April 1 (Box 46)
- Greenberg, Michael E. - Purification and Activity of the PP60 Protein Kinase, 1982 April 5 (Box 46)
- Wong,Tai Wai - Biochemical Characterization of Tyrosyl Protein Kinases in Normal and Virus-Transformed Cells, 1983 November 3 (Box 46)
- Hailman, Eric - Lipid Transfer Reactions Initiate Inflammatory Responses of Cells to Bacterial Upopolysaccharide, 1997 January 27 (Box 47)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted Material - Open in 2023
- Zhong, Zhong - STAT: Towards the Understanding of Signaling Specificity in Extracellular Ligand Induction of Gene Transcription, 1995 March 12 (Box 47)
- Kretzschmar, Marcus - Molecular Studies of RNA Polymerase II Transcription: Regulation by the NF-kB/IkB System and identification, Purification, Cloning, and Characterization of Coactivators, 1994 December (Box 47)